Guide to the James Crumley Additions
The Wittliff Collections
- 2014-140
  - Faux National "Photographic" cover for Crumley's 60th birthday [removed from frame], undated (Box 1897, Folder 14)
  - Drawing by Sheila Miles for Crumley's 60th birthday party, undated (Box 1897, Folder 15)
  - Calendars-annotated, 2005, 2008 (Box 1897, Folder 16)
  - Published writing, undated (Box 1897, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence; includes a letter from Jim Harrison and John Hickenlooper, undated (Box 1897, Folder 18)
  - Cards and drawings by Martha for Crumley, undated (Box 1897, Folder 19)
  - Scrapbook pages from John Crumley; photographs, undated (Box 1897, Folder 20)
  - "Buddha and the Death Cult"; "Montana Review of Books" baseball sporting digest, undated (Box 1897, Folder 21)
  - "Bordersnakes" reviews, undated (Box 1898, Folder 1)
  - "Bordersnakes"- "Murder Ink" catalog, and cards, undated (Box 1898, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and office papers; includes "Badwater Canyon" correspondence, blurbs; and "Flight of the Butterflies", undated (Box 1898, Folder 3)
  - Publicity/reviews, undated (Box 1898, Folder 4)
  - Book jackets- "The Mexican Tree Duck"; "The Last Good Kiss", includes proof; and "The Right Madness" (note: novel does not match cover) (Box 1898, Folder 5)
  - One case of 3½" floppy disks [24 disks], undated (Box 1898)
  - One videocassette: "A Club Med Forum in Columbus Isle" on the mystery novel: "Darkness"-a film by Patricia Desmortiers, December 2000 (Box 1898)
  - One videocassette: "L'Esprit de la Route/The Way of the Road", undated (Box 1898)
  - Two CDs: "L'Esprit de la Route/The Way of the Road", undated (Box 1898)
  - One CD: "Poets of the Tabloid Murder- talks with James Crumley", undated (Box 1898)
  - One CD: Gallacher photos of Jim Crumley, April 2004 (Box 1898)
  - One audiocassette: "An Interview with James Crumley", undated (Box 1898)
  - One whetstone in wooden box: "Buck Knives Hard Arkansas Stone #135", undated (Box 1898)
  - One "Tattered Cover" bookmark award, May 26, 2005 (Box 1898)
  - Box A: one Montana Driver's License; One New Mexico Driver's License; one military dog tag; one leather luggage tag; one set of tags for a dog; four foreign coins, undated (Box 1898, Box A)
  - One metal "Savage-Fox-Stevens-Sporting Arms" ashtray, undated (Box 1898)
  - One rock belt buckle with image of brown bear, undated (Box 1898)
  - One "Montana Centennial Commemorative" belt buckle with image of eagle, undated (Box 1898)
  - One "Montana Centennial Commemorative" belt buckle with image of grizzly bear, undated (Box 1898)
  - One "Shugrue & Milo's Bordersnakes Pilsner" beer bottle, undated (Box 1898)
  - One pair of fingerless gray knitted gloves, undated (Box 1898)
  - One "Club House Members Only" purple shirt, undated (Box 1898)
  - One "Eddie D" red Hawaiian shirt, undated (Box 1898)
  - One black alligator lizard leather belt, size 42, #20531, undated (Box 1899)
  - One pair of black suspenders, undated (Box 1899)
  - One fishing bag with gear: includes numerous fishing lures, undated (Box 1899)
  - One green fishing bag: empty, undated (Box 1899)
  - One "Hermes 3000 made in Switzerland" manual typewriter: light green/grey in carrying case-includes one sheet of paper, still loaded, reads: "a long day and not over yet…", undated (Box 1900)
  - "Marble" paper illustration, created by Martha for Crumley:16.25" x 11.5"; handmade poster: "Columbus Day 1492: Crumley Discovers America (and Texas)": 18" x 12"; oversize clipping on Crumley from "Rolling Stone": 16.5" x 8", October 5, 1978 (Box 1901, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, 1969-2000 (Box 1901, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, 2001-2009 (Box 1901, Folder 3)
  - One "IBM Correcting Selectric II" electric typewriter, brown, no case, undated (Item 1902)
  - One skull with Texas flag bikini top attached-inspired by "The Final Country" book cover: 15" x 17", undated (Item 1903)
  - One bolt-action rifle "Remington Model 788" used by Crumley: belonged to his grandfather, undated (Item 1904)
  - One mounted antler hat rack, used by Crumley (deer shot by Crumley): 20" x 15"; One wooden "South Bend" fishing net: 24" x 11", undated (Item 1905)